A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Quality Employment Unit, Office Files of Helen Neuborne FA1837
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject files, 1974-2015; 1; 15.19 Cubic Feet 40 letter size document boxes.
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) request for proposals, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 460)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) request for proposals, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 461)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) request for proposals - San Francisco Work Families Credit (WFC) Focus Groups, 2005-2007 (Box 37, Folder 462)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) request for proposals - San Antonio ACORN and Goodwill, conversation with Annie E. Casey Foundation, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 463)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP) request for proposals - Follow up, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 464)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2007-2008 (Box 37, Folder 465)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2006-2008 (Box 37, Folder 466-467)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) Supporting Work Project (SWP), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 468)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Impact of assets on benefits, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 469)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Center for Economic Progress (CEP), 2007 (Box 37, Folder 470)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Ceridian, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 471)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Community Action Project (CAP), 2007 (Box 38, Folder 472)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Family Resource Center at Gorham, New Hampshire, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 473)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Goodwill Industries of San Antonio, Texas, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 474)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Human Services Coalition, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 475)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - SF Works, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 476)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - FEI Behavioral Health/Seedco, 2006-2007 (Box 38, Folder 477)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - Step Up Savannah, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 478)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - United Way of Central Iowa, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 479)
  - Families and Work Institute (FWI) - United Way of Tucson and Southern Arizona, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 480)
  - Mott Foundation, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 481)
  - Lisa Guide, Rockefeller Family Fund (RFF), 2009 (Box 38, Folder 482)
  - Annie E. Casey Foundation (AECF) activities, 2007-2009 (Box 38, Folder 483)
  - Funders' role and activities, 2004-2007 (Box 38, Folder 484)
  - Funders' contact information and issues, 2001-2007 (Box 38, Folder 485)
  - Ford Foundation strategic planning - Discussions and memos, 2006-2009 (Box 38, Folder 486)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP) state demonstration - Urban Institute, 2008-2009 (Box 38, Folder 487)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP) state demonstration - Project on Program Simplification and Coordination, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 488)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) Phase II Evaluation - Phase II changes, 2008-2010 (Box 38, Folder 489)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) Phase II Evaluation - Data analysis, 2008-2009 (Box 38, Folder 490)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) February 2009 interim reports, 2009-2013 (Box 39, Folder 491)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) February 2009 interim reports - Reporting forms, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 492)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) February 2009 interim reports - Behavioral economics, 2006-2009 (Box 39, Folder 493)
  - Women's Program Forum (WPF) - Forum ideas, 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 494)
  - Women's Program Forum (WPF) - Take Our Daughters to Work Day, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 495)
  - Women's Program Forum (WPF), 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 496)
  - Women's Program Forum (WPF) - Ford Foundation Special Issue on Women, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 497)
  - Women's Program Forum (WPF), 1992-2008 (Box 39, Folder 498)
  - Hector Cordero-Guzman memos, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 499)
  - Helen Neuborne Echo Communications permission to use statement, 2012-2013 (Box 39, Folder 500)
  - Companion Exemption Mini-Case, 2012 (Box 39, Folder 501)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women (WOW) - Family Economic Self-Sufficiency Project, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 502)
  - Wider Opportunities for Women (WOW), 2001-2004 (Box 40, Folder 503)
  - MDRC - John Wallace paper "A vision for the Future of the Workforce Investment System", 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 504)
  - Anna Wadia and Laine Romero-Alston joint officers' meeting, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 505)
  - Quality Employment unit - Initiatives and approaches, 2009-2014 (Box 40, Folder 506)
  - Ford Foundation World Wide Meeting - Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 507)
  - Gender at Ford Foundation World Wide Meeting, 2010-2012 (Box 40, Folder 508)
  - Miscellaneous memos, correspondence, and meeting materials, 2002-2015 (Box 40, Folder 509)
  - Helen Neuborne talks to students, 2013-2014 (Box 40, Folder 510)
  - Ford Foundation Economic Opportunity and Assets Program May 2011 Evaluation, 2008-2011 (Box 40, Folder 511)
  - Pablo Farias - Meeting notes and correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 512)
  - Pablo Farias - Program strategy presentation for Ford Foundation Trustees, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 513)